Your Highness, don't worry.
Princess Consort of Rui...
She is the daughter of Prime Minister Shen.
Miss Shen's injuries
are not serious.
It's just because
she knelt for several days
and got caught in the rain,
that she fell into a coma.
I'll go
to prescribe
some tranquilizers.
Thank you.
Lou Xi.
What can I do for you, Your Highness?
Where is
her personal maid?
You mean
Zhiyan
is at Lingguo Temple, right?
You bring her here.
She can take care of Miss Shen
in the next few days.
Now?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll do it right away.
As you expected,
Prince Yu
has taken Shen Suhe to his mansion.
What should we do next?
You keep
stay by Qianzhi's side.
It's time for him to be sacrificed.
Yes.
I didn't expect
Sui'er to know the Prince.
On the day he entered the palace,
I probed him.
But his answer
was flawless.
You
don't understand the human heart.
The more he
pushes Shen Suhe away,
the more he cares about her.
Fortunately,
you helped me in advance.
Otherwise,
I really don't know
how to deal with my uncle.
I just reminded Your Majesty
that Prince Yu and Xiao Wei are close.
I didn't expect
His Majesty has set him up.
If he doesn't interrogate,
Shen will die.
Xiao Wei will be condemned
for all time.
If he does,
he'll be trapped.
His Majesty will be more suspicious of him.
I'm afraid he wants to interrogate.
My brother won't give up easily.
Then let my brother
fight with him.
When they are both hurt,
it's time for us
to catch them.
Then I
will catch you first.
Your Highness,
you've seen these things
hundreds of times.
But
the important evidence
have been stored in the Dali Temple.
We can't get in until you
accept the case.
But
since Shen Suhe came here,
rumors have been spreading.
It is said that
you have known the Prime Minister's daughter for a long time.
You came back to the capital
just for the case of Prime Minister Shen.
I didn't expect you, my nephew,
to be so good at spreading rumors.
Your Highness,
Miss Shen is awake.
Miss, you're awake.
Miss, you're finally awake.
What's wrong?
Little crybaby.
Slow down.
I was almost crushed by you.
Miss
You can't leave me behind anymore.
No matter where you go,
I'll follow you.
Well,
do you follow me to the bathroom?
I'll wait for you at the door.
Okay, okay.
Slow down.
Did His Highness bring you to the mansion
to take care of me?
Yes.
Have you met him?
What is he like?
I have met him several times,
but he always wears a mask,
and rarely speaks.
Every time he comes, he just takes a quick look at you,
and leaves when he sees you still unconscious.
He's very strange.
I also heard that
he has a face of a villain,
with a leopard head and round eyes.
There is
a scar on his face.
That's why he always wears a mask.
I had to do this.
Why do you all like to show up with a mask?
Prince Yu
Miss
Is there anything wrong?
I'm thirsty.
Get up and drink some water.
I'll go get you some water.
Miss Shen
Prince
asked me to bring you some tonic
and some new clothes and jewelry.
Miss
These are better than those in the mansion.
Of course.
These are treasures
he has collected over the years.
They may not even be found in the palace.
How can they be compared
with those in the mansion?
Thank you for your kindness.
When can I see him?
He's busy today.
When he's done,
he will come to you.
Miss Shen,
just stay here at ease.
If you need anything,
just tell me.
May I have your name?
My name is Lou Xi.
Xiao.
Lou Xiao.
Your surname is Lou, too?
I know what you want to ask.
I and the previous Lou Xi are...
are from the same place.
All the villagers in my village are surnamed Lou.
Do you know about my father's case?
Your Highness
just asked me to let you rest.
As for the rest,
I don't know much.
Sorry.
Zhiyan.
Miss.
You haven't slept well for days.
Listen to me.
Go back and have a good sleep tonight.
Miss.
You're not fully recovered yet.
Let me take care of you, okay?
Don't worry.
This is the mansion after all.
There are so many servants outside.
Today,
you must go back and have a good sleep.
Good girl.
Okay.
Then you should get some rest early.
The more you don't want to see me,
the more I want to see you.
Your Highness
Since you're here,
why don't you want to see me?
It's late at night.
Miss Shen,
you'd better go back to bed.
Prince Yu,
or
should I call you Master Lou?
You've got the wrong person.
I'm not the Master Lou you said.
If you are not him,
why do you avoid me?
Is it that
the fierce Prince Yu in the mouth of the public
afraid of a weak woman like me?
I'm right here.
What do you want to ask?
Are you really not him?
No.
Do you know him?
He's just
a shadow guard of mine.
I don't know him.
If you have nothing else to ask,
I'll take my leave.
If you're not him,
why did you bring me here,
and send Zhiyan to take care of me?
If you're not him,
why do you avoid me all the time,
and only come to see me at night?
If you're not him,
who asked for the imperial edict
to save me from here?
You've met the Consort Dowager?
Yes.
Consort Dowager Li told me personally.
It's you.
Prince Yu
asked her to get the imperial edict.
I always thought
the imperial edict to save me from Prince Rui's Mansion
was asked by the Fourth Prince.
I didn't expect
it was you.
I didn't know
the imperial edict that banished me to Lingguo Temple
was actually requested by you.
We have never met before.
How could you take such a risk?
It was my son.
He begged me so hard.
That's why
I spoke to His Majesty.
But I don't understand.
We have never met before.
Why would you risk your life to save me?
Life is precious.
The PM's Residence is doomed.
I just
want to leave a successor
for it.
Since
you've met my shadow guards,
you must know
I'm gonna clear Xiao Wei's name.
Your life
is crucial.
Saving you
is just a temporary measure.
Fine.
In that case,
show me your face under the mask.
If you're not the one I know,
I'll leave the mansion tomorrow.
From then on,
we'll have nothing to do with each other.
I'm ugly.
I'm afraid of frightening you.
No matter how ugly I am,
I'm not as bad as you.
I've seen the worst of
human nature.
Nothing can scare me.
You are him.
Why don't you admit it?
Don't forget
your identity.
You're still the Princess Consort of Rui.
Do you really
to see my face?
Yes.
What's the point of taking off the mask?
I'm not only a despised princess consort,
but also the daughter of a criminal.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't be involved.
Sorry.
I was out of line.
Please forgive me.
Now that the misunderstanding is cleared,
I have other matters to attend to.
Please excuse me.
Your Highness,
you mentioned
seeking justice for General Xiao Wei.
I believe you took me into your residence
to find an opportunity
to take over this case from the Second Prince.
However, you're concerned that His Majesty
might suspect you of colluding with the PM,
so you've been hesitant to act.
I have a plan
that can break this deadlock.
Your Highness,
are you willing to hear the details?
I didn't know Your Highness was coming,
and I apologize for not greeting you properly.
Please forgive me.
But Your Highness,
bringing so many people
to barge into our Dali Court,
what is your intention?
I have taken over the case of Shen Yi and Xiao Wei.
I would appreciate it
if you could hand over the relevant case files.
This...
This case
has always been handled
by Prince Rui.
This...
Uncle,
what brings you here to the Dali Temple today?
I'm here
to investigate the case.
Please
hand over all the files
to my mansion.
Uncle,
I was informed that
you took Shen Suhe into the mansion
and were suspected of colluding with Shen Yi.
What?
Hao'er,
Are you talking about
your princess consort?
Shen Suhe, the daughter of Prime Minister Shen.
The old lover
who has been in love with me for a thousand miles.
I have been away from the capital for many years.
I really didn't expect
that in the capital,
there are people who dare to use me
to maliciously slander and cause trouble.
They deserve to be punished.
I have found out that
the novel
was written by your princess consort,
Shen Suhe.
She has been put in prison.
After the investigation,
she will be dealt with.